{
    "id": "1d76d7c442ae449fa3b5769985431abd",
    "title": "Possessive Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Let’s go to …………………. house.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "hers",
                "she"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b85d6c64ac614134a850da9fb54df140"
        },
        {
            "question": "Is this book ....................................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "your",
                "you",
                "yours"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9ebfb271a0ca4c6da0eca1f4302f3b92"
        },
        {
            "question": "That house is ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "hers",
                "she"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "30a6ecee127c496eb5b01715f1a678fb"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you hear the mobile ring? I think it is .................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "my",
                "mine"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3d7106a4300c4b86a20b671bb82eaa2c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can we go in .................................. car?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "his"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6b527aba323e42a58434509c0c532526"
        },
        {
            "question": "Look at that dog over there. It is ................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "his"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "325675df71bc418ebbbc6ed85ac1a8d2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Look at that house over the river. It is ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "them",
                "their",
                "theirs"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "eec59c52c9ba4b00bf6b5a31d893120a"
        },
        {
            "question": "This car is ..................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "our",
                "ours",
                "us"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3cd372cbaed7407193b0e79da9c8eb08"
        },
        {
            "question": "Is this ...................................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "your",
                "yours"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5e3431b7b7e540b1972305a62ca2f791"
        },
        {
            "question": "No, it is ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "hers",
                "she"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "01d8e5298ad84e889c20fd45b5034ec7"
        }
    ]
}